SEUNGWON LEE

CONTACT

7

07826168590



aisehikaru@gmail.com



Blyth, Northumberland, UK

EDUCATION

DAELIM UNIVERSITY COLLEGE

Associate Degree in Ubiquitous Computing,

2010 - 2012

EZEN ACADEMY

UI/UX Design Bootcamp,

2017 - 2018

SEOUL GAME ACADEMY

Game Art Course,

2016 - 2018

SKILLS

Fast learning and adaptability

Strong work ethic and reliability

Web design & IT troubleshooting skills

Initiative & self-motivation

Strong attention for detail

SUMMARY

Energetic and adaptable professional from South Korea with handson experience across many roles. Native Korean speaker with intermediate English. After years of diverse jobs and self driven learning, I became a web designer. Now based in the UK, I am ready to take on any opportunity and contribute with a positive, reliable attitude.

EXPERIENCE

VARIOUS ROLES (PART-TIME, CONTRACT, TEMPORARY) 2013 - 2022 / South Korea

- Factory/Production Line Worker
- Convenience Store Manager (CU)
- Japanese Restaurant Kitchen Assistant (Katsuya)
- Shoe Store Sales Assistant (ShoePen)
- Housekeeping (hotel/accommodation)
- Office Assistant, Document Organizer (LotteSuper)
- Warehouse Staff (Coupang logistics)
- PC Café & Billiard Hall Staff
- Laptop / IT Repair Assistant (DBschenker)

BNKMAX (JUNIOR WEB DESIGNER)

Aug 2018 - Mar 2019 / South Korea

 Assisted with website layout, updates, and product listings for online shops

KOREA LUXURY APPRAISAL CENTER (WEB DESIGNER / ADMIN ASSISTANT)

Apr 2019 - Apr 2021 / South Korea

· Designed and managed shopping mall website, SEO, and content

BLANDYLAB (WEB DESIGNER & PUBLISHER)

Jun 2021 - Dec 2022, South Korea

Created product pages and managed online shop

PROPIC (SENIOR WEB DESIGNER / UI & UX SPECIALIST) Jan 2023 – Nov 2024, South Korea

- · Led e-commerce website design and branding
- Improved UI/UX based on SEO & analytics